live penalized for ten minutes
but don't touch accept if you get it
to many
this penalty sign appears when they are live
I tell you why it happened to me and why it happens to many people.
but don't touch that accept button.
before commenting
the penalty pattern being followed by tiktok
that many are penalized live
just as I was penalized I took the capture
I took this other one
capture just when he was already nine minutes and ten seconds old
then I took
this other one with twenty seconds to go before the penalty.
and finally and
Construction completed
I never closed my live
I never gave up
the live
people go into terror and go straight to the red button
without reading
without doing anything you have a red button that says accept
you are accepting the penalty you were given
and you have another one that says appeal
therefore it is necessary to read
says live was suspended for ten minutes
where
I will not be able to have gifts and certain things that tiktok warns me about.
therefore we continue live
but we will appeal and right after we appeal
goes to us
to leave
a legend
where it says I do not agree with this penalty.
now why did you do it to me
and why it is happening to many people
I just put on
to show
on screen
examples
of how they could make better and more efficient acts of sale
how to make
subliminal sale
and I started
to show
certain things
inside
from my that made a little bit of noise to tiktok
normally my live are not for direct sale
are instructive
and just at that moment tiktok said what is going on here.
this is not tiktok shop
is not paying me
we are going to penalize it
so as advice for those who engage in sales events
lower it a little bit
do not make it so
are not
so desperate
for selling at that time and talk more with the public
give more applications
benefits such as
use these products
and not so much
as a desperate action in that act of trying to get him out of the
benefit to this product
but tell me
you are being penalized live
I read you in the comments